6,Warner Bros. Pictures,/film/production_company/films,Saving Shiloh,"what movie is produced by warner bros.
10,Detroit,/location/location/people_born_here,J. Moss,"who is a musician born in detroit
11,RYNA,/music/artist/origin,Manchester,"Which city did the artist ryna originate in
",<ORG>RYNA</ORG> were a rock band from <LOC>Manchester</LOC>,<LOC>Manchester</LOC> is a city in Greater <LOC>Manchester</LOC>
13,Mera Shikar,/film/film/language,Hindi,"what is the language in which mera shikar was filmed in
15,Chicago,/location/location/events,Battle of Fort Dearborn,"Whats the name of a battle that happened in chicago
",<ORG>Chicago</ORG>,The <MISC>Battle of Fort Dearborn</MISC> was an engagement between <LOC>United States</LOC> troops and <MISC>Potawatomi Native Americans</MISC> that occurred on August 15
",<ORG>Howell Cheney Technical High School</ORG>,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
18,Great Patriotic War,/military/military_conflict/military_personnel_involved,Andrey Vlasov,"which red army general was involved in the great patriotic war?
",The <MISC>Great Patriotic War</MISC> is a term used in <LOC>Russia</LOC> and some other former republics of the <LOC>Soviet Union</LOC> to describe the conflict fought during the period from 22 June 1941 to 9 May 1945 along the many fronts of the <LOC>Eastern Front</LOC> of <MISC>World War II</MISC>,<PER>Andrey Andreyevich Vlasov</PER> was a <ORG>Soviet Red Army</ORG> general and <ORG>Nazi</ORG> collaborator. During <MISC>World War II</MISC>
",<PER>Mike Twellman</PER> was a <LOC>U.S.</LOC> soccer defender who played two seasons in the <ORG>North American Soccer League</ORG>,In the sport of association football
25,England,/location/location/contains,G-A-Y,"what is a name of gay night club in england
27,Italy,/location/location/contains,San Giovanni d'Asso,"Name a location in italy
",<ORG>Italy</ORG>,<LOC>San Giovanni d’Asso</LOC> is a frazione of the comune of <LOC>Montalcino</LOC>
28,Ellen Swallow Richards,/people/person/nationality,United States,"what is ellen swallow richards's nationality?
",<PER>Ellen Henrietta Swallow Richards</PER> was an industrial and safety engineer,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
30,Nepal,/location/location/contains,Janakpur,"Name a city in Nepal.
",<ORG>Nepal</ORG>,<LOC><LOC>Janakpur</LOC>dham</LOC> or <LOC>Janakpur</LOC> is a sub-metropolitan city in <LOC>Dhanusha District</LOC>
32,Strategy game,/media_common/media_genre/child_genres,Grand strategy wargame,"What is a child genre of strategy game
",A strategy game or strategic game is a game in which the players' uncoerced,A grand strategy wargame or simply grand strategy game is a wargame that places focus on grand strategy: military strategy at the level of movement and use of a nation state or empire's resources. 
",<MISC>Elementary</MISC> is an <MISC>American</MISC> procedural drama television series that presented a contemporary update of Sir <PER>Arthur Conan Doyle</PER>'s character <PER>Sherlock Holmes</PER>. It was created by <PER>Robert Doherty</PER> and starred <PER>Jonny Lee Miller</PER> as <PER>Sherlock Holmes</PER> and <PER>Lucy Liu</PER> as Dr. <PER>Joan Watson</PER>. The series premiered on <ORG>CBS</ORG> on September 27,<MISC>English</MISC> is a <MISC>West Germanic</MISC> language of the <MISC>Indo-European</MISC> language family
","<PER>James <PER>Hendry</PER></PER> was Regius Professor of Midwifery at the <ORG>University of Glasgow</ORG> from 1943 until his death in 1945.
45,Wyatt Earp's Revenge,/film/film/genre,Western,"what type a film is wyatt earps revenge
","<PER>Wyatt Earp</PER>'s Revenge is a 2012 <MISC>American Western</MISC> film about the legendary lawman <PER>Wyatt Earp</PER>.
47,Jean Genet,/influence/influence_node/influenced,James Salter,"who did jean genet influence
",<PER>Jean Genet</PER> was a <MISC>French</MISC> novelist,<PER>James Arnold Horowitz</PER>
51,Tomadino language,/language/human_language/main_country,Indonesia,"What country utilizes the tomadino language
",<MISC>Tomadino</MISC> is an <MISC>Austronesian</MISC> language of <LOC>Central Sulawesi</LOC>,<ORG>Indonesia</ORG>
57,Black Star at the Point of Darkness,/music/album/artist,Paul Bowles,"What artist includes black star at the point of darkness in his work?
",<MISC>Black Star at the Point of Darkness</MISC> is a spoken word album by <MISC>American</MISC> composer and author <PER>Paul Bowles</PER>,<PER>Paul Frederic Bowles</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> expatriate composer
61,Serge Gainsbourg,/music/artist/album,Jane Birkin &amp; Serge Gainsbourg,"Name an album by serge gainsbourg
",<PER>Serge Gainsbourg</PER> was a <MISC>French</MISC> musician,"<PER>Jane Birkin</PER>/<PER>Serge Gainsbourg</PER> is a 1969 collaborative studio album by <PER>Serge Gainsbourg</PER> and <PER>Jane Birkin</PER>. It was originally released by <ORG>Fontana Records</ORG>. It includes ""Je t'aime... moi non plus"""
63,Laura Ingalls Wilder,/book/author/works_written,A Little House Traveler,"what is a book by laura ingalls wilder 
",<PER>Laura Elizabeth Ingalls Wilder</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> writer,A Little House Traveler: Writings from <PER>Laura Ingalls Wilder</PER>'s <MISC>Journeys Across America</MISC> is a collection of early writings by <PER>Laura Ingalls Wilder</PER>
65,The Second of May 1808,/visual_art/artwork/support,Canvas,"what artwork medium is used for the second of may 1808
68,Internal medicine,/book/book_subject/works,Migraine,"What's a book that talks about internal medicine
",Internal medicine or general internal medicine is the medical specialty dealing with the prevention,<MISC>Migraine</MISC> is the first book written by <PER>Oliver Sacks</PER>
70,Fall Heads Roll,/music/album/genre,Post-punk,"What type of music fall heads roll
72,Endless Love,/film/film/cinematography,David Watkin,"Who was the cinematographer for the film endless love?
",<MISC>Endless Love</MISC> is a 1981 <MISC>American</MISC> romantic drama film directed by <PER>Franco Zeffirelli</PER>,<PER>David Watkin BSC</PER> was an <MISC>English</MISC> cinematographer
76,Brandon Reilly,/music/artist/genre,Indie rock,"what musical genre does  brandon reilly create
77,Notre Dame Fighting Irish men's basketball,/sports/sports_team/sport,Basketball,"What sport does notre dame fighting irish men's basketball play
",The <LOC>Notre Dame</LOC> Fighting Irish Men's Basketball team is the intercollegiate men's basketball program representing the <ORG>University of <LOC>Notre Dame</LOC></ORG> in <LOC>Notre Dame</LOC>,Basketball is a team sport in which two teams
79,Kenneth Hsu,/people/person/nationality,China,"What nationality is Kenneth Hsu?
",<PER>Kenneth Jinghwa Hsu</PER> Ph.D,<ORG>China</ORG>
81,Psychological thriller,/film/film_genre/films_in_this_genre,Lightning Bug,"whats an example of a psychological thriller
",<MISC>Lightning Bug</MISC> is a 2004 coming of age drama film. It is the debut film by writer/director and <MISC>SFX</MISC> makeup artist <PER>Robert Green <PER>Hall</PER></PER>. The film a fictionalized account of <PER>Hall</PER>'s own childhood and entry into special effects makeup for film and television. It was filmed on location <LOC>Fairview</LOC>
82,Hungary,/location/location/contains,Belezna,"whats a city in hungary
84,Rudi Ball,/people/person/place_of_birth,Berlin,"where in germany was rudi ball born in?
87,Cologne,/film/film_location/featured_in_films,Engel &amp; Joe,"which movie featured cologne 
90,Bodish languages,/language/language_family/languages,Gurung language,"what language comes from bodish languages
",<PER>Bodish</PER>,<MISC>Gurung</MISC> language is spoken by the <MISC>Gurung</MISC> people of <LOC>Nepal</LOC>. The total number of all <MISC>Gurung</MISC> speakers in <LOC>Nepal</LOC> was 227
91,Oxytetracycline,/medicine/drug/route_of_administration,Eye drop,"how do you administer oxytetracycline?
92,Romanians,/people/ethnicity/geographic_distribution,Romania,"where would you find romanians
93,Last Hurrah for Chivalry,/media_common/netflix_title/netflix_genres,Yue Chinese,"what netflix genre is last hurrah for chivalry?
",The <LOC>Argentine Sea</LOC> is a marginal sea of the <LOC>Atlantic Ocean</LOC> adjacent to the southern tip of <LOC>South America</LOC>. It ranges from the mouth of the estuary of the <LOC>Río de la Plata</LOC> in the north to the <LOC>Isla de los Estados</LOC> in the south,<ORG>Argentina</ORG>
",<PER>Harry Bouton Blackstone Jr.</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> stage magician,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
105,Destroy the Machines,/music/album/release_type,Album,"in what format was destroy the machines released
106,J. H. Thomas,/people/deceased_person/place_of_cremation,Golders Green Crematorium,"Where was james henry thomas cremated? 
109,Alternative hip hop,/music/genre/artists,Tommy Guerrero,"Who is an artist known for alternative hip hop?
110,8: The Mormon Proposition,/film/film/subjects,Mormon,"what is the topic of the movie 8: the mormon proposition
113,The Loves of the Gods,/visual_art/artwork/artist,Annibale Carracci,"who created the loves of the gods
",The <MISC>Loves of the Gods</MISC> is a monumental fresco cycle,<PER>Annibale Carracci</PER> was an <MISC>Italian</MISC> painter and instructor
115,Vitas,/music/artist/origin,Daugavpils,"where is the artist vitas  from
",<PER>Vitaly Vladasovich Grachev</PER>,<LOC>Daugavpils</LOC> is a city in south-eastern <LOC>Latvia</LOC>
116,Aguadulce,/location/location/containedby,Spain,"where is aguadulce located?
",<LOC>Aguadulce</LOC> is a municipality in <LOC>Seville</LOC>. In 2005,<LOC>Spain</LOC> or the Kingdom of <LOC>Spain</LOC>
",Rugby union,<PER>Liam Justin Messam</PER> is a <LOC>New Zealand</LOC> rugby union player who plays TOP14 for <ORG>RC Toulonnais</ORG>. In <ORG>Super Rugby</ORG>
126,National Film Board of Canada,/film/production_company/films,The Sparky Book,"What is a film produced by the national film board of canada?
128,The Golden Age,/music/album/release_type,Album,"Is the golden age an album or dvd
129,Eugênio Sales,/people/person/gender,Male,"what gender does eugênio sales identify as 
132,Chicago,/location/location/people_born_here,Alson S. Clark,"Name a person born in chicago.
",<ORG>Chicago</ORG>,<PER>Alson Skinner Clark</PER> was an <MISC>American Impressionist</MISC> painter best remembered for his landscapes. He was also a photographer
","<PER>John Humbird <PER>Duffey</PER> Jr.</PER> was a <LOC><LOC>Washington</LOC> D.C.</LOC> based bluegrass musician.
139,7 Wishes,/music/album/artist,Night Ranger,"who is the artist on seven wishes
",<MISC>7 Wishes</MISC> is the third studio album by the <MISC>American</MISC> hard rock band <ORG>Night Ranger</ORG>,<ORG>Night Ranger</ORG> is an <MISC>American</MISC> hard rock band from <LOC>San Francisco</LOC> formed in 1979 that gained popularity during the 1980s with a series of albums and singles. 
140,Gangs of New York,/film/film/music,Howard Shore,"who wrote the music for gangs of new york
",<MISC>Gangs of New York</MISC> is a 2002 <MISC>American</MISC> historical drama film directed by <PER>Martin Scorsese</PER> and written by <PER>Jay Cocks</PER>,<PER>Howard Leslie Shore OC</PER> is a <MISC>Canadian</MISC> composer and conductor noted for his film scores. He has composed the scores for over 80 films
143,"Is It Love? Ultra Naté Best Remixes, Vol. 1",/music/album/album_content_type,Remix album,"what types of album is the best remixes, vol. 1
",<MISC>Is It Love</MISC>? <MISC>Ultra Naté</MISC> Best Remixes,A remix album is an album consisting of remixes or rerecorded versions of an artist's earlier released material. The first act who employed the format was <MISC>American</MISC> singer-songwriter <PER>Harry Nilsson</PER>. 
144,Moderat,/music/artist/origin,Berlin,"What is moderat's origin?
",<PER>Louis Napoleon Parker</PER> was an <MISC>English</MISC> dramatist,<MISC>Disraeli</MISC> is a 1929 <MISC>American</MISC> historical film directed by <PER>Alfred E. Green</PER>
148,Get Damned,/music/album/genre,Deathcore,"What genre of music is on the album get damned
",<MISC>Frontpage</MISC> is the title of a <MISC>Malaysian</MISC> television drama created by <PER>Kabir Bhatia</PER> and <PER>Mira Mustaffa</PER>,Action fiction is the literary genre that includes spy novels
152,Michelle Ashford,/tv/tv_writer/episodes_written,Pilot,"what is an episode written by michelle ashford
156,Francis Ford Coppola,/film/music_contributor/film,Apocalypse Now,"what movies has francis ford coppola contributed music to
",<PER>Francis Ford Coppola</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> film director,<MISC>Apocalypse Now</MISC> is a 1979 <MISC>American</MISC> epic psychological war film directed and produced by <PER>Francis Ford Coppola</PER> and starring <PER>Marlon Brando</PER>
160,Communist Party of Britain,/government/political_party/ideology,Communism,"which is the main ideology of the communist party of britain?
",The <ORG><ORG>Communist Party of</ORG> Britain</ORG> is a communist party in <LOC>Great Britain</LOC> which emerged from a dispute between <MISC>Eurocommunists</MISC> and <MISC>Marxist-Leninists</MISC> in the <ORG>Communist Party of</ORG> <LOC>Great Britain</LOC> in 1988. ,<MISC>Communism</MISC> is a far-left philosophical
161,Irvin Shapiro,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,New York,"irvin shapiro passed away in which city?
",<PER>Irvin Shapiro</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> producer,<LOC>New York</LOC>
162,Center,/basketball/basketball_position/players,Aleksey Savrasenko,"what former basketball played the center (basketball) position
",The center,"<PER>Alexey Dmitrievitch Savrasenko</PER> is a retired <MISC>Russian-Greek</MISC> professional basketball player. He played at the center position.
Because of <MISC>half-Greek</MISC> origin from his mother's side"
164,Folk music,/music/genre/albums,The Movie Songbook,"what album has folk music?
165,Thunderbolt and Lightfoot,/film/film/written_by,Michael Cimino,"Who wrote the film thunderbolt and lightfoot?
",<MISC>Thunderbolt and Lightfoot</MISC> is a 1974 <MISC>American</MISC> crime comedy film written and directed by <PER>Michael Cimino</PER> and starring <PER>Clint Eastwood</PER>,<PER>Michael Cimino</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> filmmaker. He achieved fame as the director of <MISC>The Deer Hunter</MISC>
166,John Morris Russell,/people/person/place_of_birth,Cleveland,"where in the united states was john morris russell born
",<PER>John Morris Russell</PER>,<ORG>Cleveland</ORG>
167,Imam Mustafayev,/people/person/gender,Male,"what is imam mustafayev's gender
",<PER>Anthony Lane</PER> is a <MISC>British</MISC> journalist,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
","<PER>Tamara <PER>Oudyn</PER></PER> is an <MISC>Australian</MISC> television presenter and reporter.
<PER>Oudyn</PER> currently presents <ORG>ABC News Victoria</ORG> from Sunday to Thursday.",<ORG>Australia</ORG>
173,Oliver Duff,/people/person/place_of_birth,New Zealand,"Where was oliver duff born
174,Fausto Fawcett,/people/person/gender,Male,"what is fausto fawcett's gender
175,Robert Roth,/music/artist/genre,Alternative rock,"what type of music is robert roth known for?
177,Sikorsky HH-60 Jayhawk,/aviation/aircraft_model/manufacturer,Sikorsky Aircraft,"who is the manufacturer of sikorsky hh-60 jayhawk?
183,Webbie,/music/artist/label,Atlantic Records,"which recording label is webbie with?
185,Chokoloskee,/location/hud_county_place/county,Collier County,"What county has jurisdiction over chokoloskee, florida
",<PER>Morrell John Berry</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> former government official who was named President of the <MISC>American</MISC> Australian Association in 2016. ,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
188,Joseph Meyer,/people/person/profession,Lawyer,"What is joseph meyer's job
191,Home,/book/book/genre,Novel,"What kind of book is home?
",<MISC>Home</MISC> is a novel written by the <MISC>Pulitzer Prize-winning</MISC> <MISC>American</MISC> author <PER>Marilynne Robinson</PER>. Published in 2008,A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction
195,Kolo Touré,/people/person/ethnicity,Mandinka people,"kolo touré is of what ethnic background
",<PER>Kolo Abib Touré</PER> is an <MISC>Ivorian</MISC> professional football coach and former player. He played as a defender for <ORG>Arsenal</ORG>,The <MISC>Mandinka</MISC> or <MISC><LOC>Mali</LOC>nke</MISC> are a <MISC>West African</MISC> ethnic group primarily found in southern <LOC>Mali</LOC>
196,MLDonkey,/computer/software/software_genre,Peer-to-peer,"what kinds of software is mldonkey
",<MISC>MLDonkey</MISC> is an open-source,Peer-to-peer computing or networking is a distributed application architecture that partitions tasks or workloads between peers. Peers are equally privileged
",<MISC>Cosmic Ray</MISC> is a 1962 <MISC>American</MISC> experimental short film directed by <PER>Bruce Conner</PER>.,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
199,Lorenzo Maitani,/people/person/nationality,Italy,"what is the nationality of lorenzo maitani?
","<PER>Lorenzo Maitani</PER> was the <MISC>Italian</MISC> architect and sculptor primarily responsible for the construction and decoration of the façade of <ORG>Orvieto Cathedral</ORG>.
",<ORG>Italy</ORG>
",<LOC>Zou</LOC> is one of the twelve departments of <LOC>Benin</LOC>,<LOC>Bohicon</LOC> is a city in <LOC>Benin</LOC>
207,In the Line of Fire: A Memoir,/book/book/genre,Memoir,"what genre is the book in the line of fire: a memoir
208,Alan Pierson,/people/person/gender,Male,"What is Alan Pierson's gender?
210,The Hydrofoil Mystery,/book/book/genre,Thriller,"what is the genre of the book the hydrofoil mystery
",The <MISC>Hydrofoil Mystery</MISC> was written in 1999 by <MISC>Canadian</MISC> author <PER>Eric Walters</PER>. It is about a teenage boy named <PER>Billy McCracken</PER> whose mother arranges for him to go away for the summer to work with none other than the well-known inventor of the telephone,Thriller is a genre of fiction
211,Cube 2: Sauerbraten,/cvg/computer_videogame/cvg_genre,Action game,"which video game genre is sauerbraten (game)
212,Franz Roh,/people/person/nationality,Germany,"What was the nationality of  franz roh
",<PER>Franz Roh</PER>,<ORG>Germany</ORG>
215,Jerry Seinfeld,/influence/influence_node/influenced,Steve Hofstetter,"Who influenced jerry seinfeld
",<PER>Jerome Allen Seinfeld</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> stand-up comedian,<PER>Steven Ira Hofstetter</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> stand-up comedian. As of May 2022
216,Photography,/visual_art/visual_art_form/artists,Robert Adams,"which photography artist is best known for the american west landscape?
",Photography is the art,<PER>Robert Adams</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> photographer who has focused on the changing landscape of the <MISC>American</MISC> West. His work first came to prominence in the mid-1970s through his book <MISC>The New West</MISC> and his participation in the exhibition New Topographics: Photographs of a Man-Altered Landscape in 1975. 
221,Huron County,/location/us_county/hud_county_place,Wakeman,"what is a city located in huron county
227,Murder,/people/cause_of_death/people,Fred Lane,"Which football player's cause of death was murder?
229,Italy,/location/location/contains,Avetrana,"name a town and comune in italy 
",<ORG>Italy</ORG>,<LOC>Avetrana</LOC> is a town and comune in the province of <LOC>Taranto</LOC>
233,Satire,/film/film_genre/films_in_this_genre,Blaumilch Canal,"what is a satire film from 1969?
",Satire is a genre of the visual,<MISC>Blaumilch Canal</MISC> is a 1969 <MISC>Israeli</MISC> comedy satire written and directed by <PER>Ephraim Kishon</PER>
",<LOC>Lake Belt Township</LOC> is a township in <LOC>Martin County</LOC>,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
241,Knife Edge,/film/film/genre,Supernatural,"what genre is knife edge 
243,James Gillespie,/people/deceased_person/place_of_burial,Congressional Cemetery,"where was  james gillespie buried
","<PER>James <PER>Gillespie</PER></PER> was a <MISC>Democratic-Republican</MISC> <LOC>U.S.</LOC> Congressman from <LOC>North Carolina</LOC> between 1793 and 1799.
There is some uncertainty about <PER>Gillespie</PER>'s birthplace. ",The <LOC>Congressional Cemetery</LOC>
244,Pittsburgh,/location/location/people_born_here,Eve Gordon,"who was born in pittsburgh
246,Big Sugar,/music/album/genre,Blues,"is big sugar a blues or contemporary rhythm and blues album 
","Dr. Robert ""Bob"" <PER>Williams</PER> is a former <MISC>American</MISC> football player for the <ORG>University of Notre Dame</ORG>.
<PER>Williams</PER> won three championships with G.A.R. Memorial High School in <LOC>Wilkes-Barre</LOC>",The quarterback
262,Guitar,/music/instrument/instrumentalists,St. Vincent,"who is an instrumentalist that plays the guitar
265,The City in the Autumn Stars,/book/written_work/author,Michael Moorcock,"Who wrote the book the city in the autumn stars
",<MISC>The City in the Autumn Stars</MISC>: Being a Continuation of the Story of the <PER>Von Bek</PER> Family and Its Association With <PER>Lucifer</PER>,<PER>Michael John Moorcock</PER> is an <MISC>English</MISC> writer
266,John of Gaunt,/people/person/parents,Philippa of Hainault,"Who was a parent of john of gaunt, 1st duke of lancaster
",<PER>John of Gaunt</PER>,<PER>Philippa of Hainault</PER> was Queen of <LOC>England</LOC> as the wife and political adviser of King <PER>Edward III</PER>. She acted as regent in 1346
267,Chris Cash,/people/person/nationality,United States,"chris cash is what nationality
",<PER>Christopher James <PER>Cash</PER></PER> is the Assistant Secondary Coach in charge of the cornerbacks for the <ORG>Seattle Seahawks</ORG> of the <ORG>National Football League</ORG>. <PER>Cash</PER> played professionally for the <ORG>Detroit Lions</ORG> and <ORG>Atlanta Falcons</ORG>.,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
269,33a,/music/artist/origin,Tbilisi,"what is the origin of the artist 33a?
",<ORG>33a</ORG> is a <MISC>Georgian</MISC> folk-rock band founded in <LOC>Tbilisi</LOC> in 1994. The band combines <MISC>Georgian</MISC> and <MISC>French</MISC> folk influences with pop and reggae elements. They chiefly perform in <MISC>Georgian</MISC> and <MISC>French</MISC>. ,<LOC>Tbilisi</LOC>
",<MISC>Love on a Diet</MISC> is a 2001 <LOC>Hong Kong</LOC> romantic comedy film produced and directed by <PER>Johnnie To</PER> and <PER>Wai Ka-fai</PER>,<LOC>Hong Kong</LOC>
271,Mike Nock,/music/group_member/instruments_played,Jazz piano,"which music instrument is played by mike nock
292,Open Air Stereo,/music/artist/label,Epic Records,"What record label signed the artist open air stereo
295,Joshua C.S.,/people/person/gender,Male,"what is joshua smith's gender
296,Rapture Ruckus,/music/artist/label,BEC Recordings,"What label is rapture ruckus  signed to
",<ORG>Rapture Ruckus</ORG> was a <MISC>Christian</MISC> hip hop and rock band from <LOC>Wellington</LOC>,"<ORG>BEC Recordings</ORG> is a <MISC>Christian</MISC> rock record label that is an imprint of Tooth &amp; Nail Records. The label was formed in 1997 in partnership with the EMI <MISC>Christian</MISC> Music Group.
"
297,Rob Schmidt,/film/director/film,Crime and Punishment in Suburbia,"Which film did rob schmidt direct?
",<PER>Rob Schmidt Barracano</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> filmmaker. His film credits include <MISC>Wrong Turn</MISC> and <MISC>Crime and Punishment in Suburbia</MISC>. He also created a pilot called <MISC>American</MISC> Town for <ORG>Twentieth Century Fox</ORG>. ,<MISC>Crime and Punishment in Suburbia</MISC> is a 2000 film directed by <PER>Rob Schmidt</PER> and starring <PER>Monica Keena</PER>
301,Psychedelic rock,/music/genre/albums,Made In California,"What's an example of a psychedelic rock album
",Psychedelic rock is a rock music genre that is inspired,<MISC>Made in California</MISC> is a compilation box set by the <ORG>Beach Boys</ORG>
302,American Airlines Flight 625,/aviation/airliner_accident/operator,American Airlines,"who was the operator of the american airlines flight 625
304,Get a Clue,/film/film/genre,Whodunit,"what movie genre is get a clue 
","<MISC>Get a Clue</MISC> is a 1997 film based on the <MISC>Newbery Medal-winning</MISC> book <MISC>The Westing Game</MISC>.
The film draws young viewers into the strange mysteries encountered by 13-year-old <PER>Turtle Wexler</PER> and her sister",A whodunit or whodunnit is a complex plot-driven variety of detective fiction in which the puzzle regarding who committed the crime is the main focus. 
311,Funk,/music/genre/albums,Up All Night,"What is an example of a funk album?
312,Ottilie Assing,/people/person/nationality,Germany,"Where is ottilie assing from?
",<PER>Ottilie Davida Assing</PER> was a 19th-century <MISC>German-American</MISC> feminist,<ORG>Germany</ORG>
313,Taketomi,/location/location/containedby,Japan,"what country is  taketomi apart of
314,Wipers,/music/artist/origin,Portland,"What is wipers's orgin
317,Elmer Verner McCollum,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,Lawrence,"where did  elmer verner mccollum pass away
",<PER>Elmer Verner <PER>McCollum</PER></PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> biochemist known for his work on the influence of diet on health. <PER>McCollum</PER> is also remembered for starting the first rat colony in the <LOC>United States</LOC> to be used for nutrition research. ,<LOC>Lawrence</LOC> is the county seat of <LOC>Douglas County</LOC>
319,Azerbaijanis in the United Kingdom,/people/ethnicity/languages_spoken,Turkish language,"Which language do azerbaijanis in the united kingdom speak
",<MISC><MISC>Azerbaijani</MISC>s</MISC> in the <LOC>United Kingdom</LOC> are a small <MISC>Azerbaijani</MISC> diaspora in the <LOC>United Kingdom</LOC>,<MISC>Turkish</MISC>
322,The Diane Rehm Show,/broadcast/content/genre,Talk radio,"what type of show is the diane rehm show
323,Australia,/location/location/contains,Cobar,"Name a location within australia
",<ORG>Australia</ORG>,<LOC>Cobar</LOC> is a town in central western <LOC>New South Wales</LOC>
327,Samwise Gamgee,/book/book_character/appears_in_book,The Fellowship of the Ring,"Which book does samwise gamgee appear in
",<PER>Samwise Gamgee</PER> is a fictional character in J. R. R. Tolkien's <LOC>Middle-earth</LOC>. A hobbit,<MISC>The Fellowship of the Ring</MISC> is the first of three volumes of the epic novel <MISC>The Lord of the Rings</MISC> by the <MISC>English</MISC> author J. R. R. Tolkien. It is followed by <MISC>The Two Towers</MISC> and <MISC>The Return of the King</MISC>. It takes place in the fictional universe of <LOC>Middle-earth</LOC>
332,Pilot,/tv/tv_series_episode/series,Millennium,"Which series has a pilot episode?
336,Matsumoto Castle,/architecture/building/building_function,Castle,"what is the function of matsumoto castle
",<MISC>Stealing a Nation</MISC> is a 2004 <ORG>Granada Television</ORG> documentary about the <MISC>British</MISC>–<MISC>American</MISC> clandestine operation that saw the expulsion of the <MISC>Chagossian</MISC> population who have lived on <LOC>Diego Garcia</LOC> and neighbouring islands since the late 18th century. ,The <LOC>United Kingdom of Great Britain</LOC> and <LOC>Northern Ireland</LOC>
339,Carlos Johnson,/music/artist/genre,Blues,"which type of music genre does carlos johnson play in?
341,Thomas Sully,/people/person/place_of_birth,Horncastle,"Which town was thomas sully born? 
",<PER>Thomas Sully</PER> was an portrait painter in the <LOC>United States</LOC>. Born in <LOC>Great Britain</LOC>,<LOC>Horncastle</LOC> is a town and civil parish in the <LOC>East Lindsey</LOC> district in <LOC>Lincolnshire</LOC>
342,D. A. Pennebaker,/film/cinematographer/film,The War Room,"which documentary did d. a. pennebaker provide the cinematography?
",<PER>Donn Alan Pennebaker</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> documentary filmmaker and one of the pioneers of direct cinema. Performing arts and politics were his primary subjects. ,<MISC>The War Room</MISC> is a 1993 <MISC>American</MISC> documentary film about <PER>Bill Clinton</PER>'s campaign for President of the <LOC>United States</LOC> during the 1992 <LOC>United States</LOC> presidential election. Directed by <PER>Chris Hegedus</PER> and <PER>D. A. Pennebaker</PER>
361,New Hampshire Red,/base/petbreeds/chicken_breed/primary_use,Egg,"what is the primary use of the chicken breed new hampshire?
",The <MISC><LOC>New Hampshire</LOC> Red</MISC> or <LOC>New Hampshire</LOC> is an <MISC>American</MISC> breed of chicken. It was developed in the early twentieth century in the state of <LOC>New Hampshire</LOC> by selective breeding of <LOC>Rhode</LOC> <MISC>Island Red</MISC> stock; no other breed was involved. ,Eggs are laid by female animals of many different species
363,Bob Woodward,/people/person/parents,Alfred E. Woodward,"who is the parent of bob woodward?
","<PER>Robert Upshur Woodward</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> investigative journalist. He started working for <ORG>The Washington Post</ORG> as a reporter in 1971 and currently holds the title of associate editor.
",<PER>Alfred Eno Woodward II</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> attorney and jurist who served as the Chief Judge of the <ORG>18th Judicial Circuit Court</ORG>
367,Gregory La Cava,/film/director/film,Symphony of Six Million,"what film does gregory la cava direct?
368,Celtic rock,/music/genre/artists,Great Big Sea,"what artist makes celtic rock?
",Celtic rock is a genre of folk rock,<ORG>Great Big Sea</ORG> was a <MISC>Canadian</MISC> folk rock band from <LOC>Newfoundland</LOC> and <LOC>Labrador</LOC>
373,Barbara Cook,/people/person/place_of_birth,Atlanta,"What is the place of barbara cook's birth?
374,You're in the Navy Now,/film/film/subjects,World War II,"which subject is the film you're in the navy now about
",You're in the Navy Now is a 1951 <MISC>American</MISC> war drama film about the <ORG>United States Navy</ORG> in the first months of <MISC>World War II</MISC>. The film was directed by <PER>Henry Hathaway</PER> and stars <PER>Gary Cooper</PER> as a new officer wanting duty at sea but who is instead assigned to an experimental project without much hope of success. ,<MISC>World War II</MISC> or the <MISC>Second World War</MISC>
375,The Jack Bull,/film/film/film_format,35 mm movie film,"What kind of film was the jack bull filmed on
",The <MISC>Jack Bull</MISC> is a 1999 <MISC>American Western</MISC> television film directed by <PER>John Badham</PER> and written by <PER>Dick Cusack</PER>. It is loosely based on <PER>Heinrich von Kleist</PER>'s novel,35 mm film is a film gauge used in filmmaking
",The <ORG>National Academy of Design</ORG> is an honorary association of <MISC>American</MISC> artists,The <ORG>National Academy of Design</ORG> is an honorary association of <MISC>American</MISC> artists
379,Marshallville,/location/location/containedby,Kentucky,"marshallville, kentucky is an unincorporated community in what  state?
",<LOC>Marshallville</LOC> is an unincorporated community within <LOC>Magoffin County</LOC>,<ORG>Kentucky</ORG>
382,Interactive fiction,/cvg/cvg_genre/games,The President Is Missing,"What is the name of an interactive fiction game?
",Interactive fiction,"<MISC>The President Is Missing</MISC> is a computer simulation game written by <PER>Paul Norman</PER> for the <MISC>Commodore 64</MISC> and published by <ORG>Cosmi</ORG> in 1988. The game came with an audio cassette with different recordings and an anonymous note signed by ""<PER>Saduj</PER>""."
",<PER>José Antonio Domínguez Bandera</PER>,<LOC>Spain</LOC> or the Kingdom of <LOC>Spain</LOC>
393,Plum Island Animal Disease Center,/location/location/containedby,Plum Island,"where in new york is building 101 located 
",<ORG>Plum Island Animal Disease Center</ORG> is a <LOC>United States</LOC> federal research facility dedicated to the study of foreign animal diseases of livestock. ,<LOC>Plum Island</LOC> is an island in the town of <LOC>Southold</LOC> in <LOC>Suffolk County</LOC>
",<PER>Leslie John Ralston</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> boxer.,Boxing is a combat sport in which two people
402,Adario Strange,/people/person/gender,Male,"is adario strange male or female
409,Wittlich,/location/location/people_born_here,Hanin Elias,"Who is someone born in wittlich
420,Shmuel Salant,/people/person/place_of_birth,Białystok,"which city was shmuel salant born
",<PER>Shmuel Salant</PER> served as the <MISC>Ashkenazi</MISC> Chief Rabbi of <LOC>Jerusalem</LOC> for almost 70 years. He was a renowned <MISC>Talmudist</MISC> and <MISC>Torah</MISC> scholar.,<LOC>Białystok</LOC> is the largest city in northeastern <LOC>Poland</LOC> and the capital of the <LOC>Podlaskie Voivodeship</LOC>. It is the tenth-largest city in <LOC>Poland</LOC>
421,Summertide,/book/written_work/author,Charles Sheffield,"who authored summertide
",<MISC>Summertide</MISC> is a science fiction novel by <MISC>American</MISC> writer <PER>Charles Sheffield</PER>,<PER>Charles Sheffield</PER> was an <MISC>English-born</MISC> mathematician
422,Naser al-Din Shah Qajar,/people/deceased_person/cause_of_death,Murder,"How was naser al-din shah qajar killed
",<PER>Naser al-Din Shah Qajar</PER> was the Shah of <LOC>Qajar Iran</LOC> from 5 September 1848 to 1 May 1896 when he was assassinated. He was the son of <PER>Mohammad Shah Qajar</PER> and <PER>Malek Jahan Khanom</PER> and the third longest reigning monarch in <MISC>Iranian</MISC> history after <PER>Shapur II</PER> of the <PER>Sassanid</PER> dynasty and <PER>Tahmasp I</PER> of the <PER>Safavid</PER> dynasty. ,Murder is the unlawful killing of another human without justification or valid excuse
425,Ronnie Burns,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,Pacific Palisades,"Which city did ronnie burns die in
",<PER>Ronald Jon Burns</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> television actor. He is primarily remembered as the son of comedians <PER>George Burns</PER> and <PER><PER>Gracie</PER> Allen</PER> and a regular cast member of The <PER>George Burns</PER> and <PER><PER>Gracie</PER> Allen</PER> Show on <ORG>CBS</ORG>.,<LOC>Pacific Palisades</LOC> is a neighborhood in the <LOC>Westside</LOC> region of <LOC>Los Angeles</LOC>
",A civil engineer is a person who practices civil engineering – the application of planning,"<PER>George Stephenson</PER> was an <MISC>English</MISC> civil engineer and mechanical engineer. Renowned as the ""Father of Railways"""
433,Political science,/book/book_subject/works,The Prosecution of George W. Bush for Murder,"What's a book written about political science
",Political science is the scientific study of politics. It is a social science dealing with systems of governance and power,<MISC>The</MISC> <MISC>Prosecution of George W. Bush for Murder</MISC> is a 2008 book by <PER>Vincent Bugliosi</PER>
439,Towns County,/symbols/namesake/named_after,George W. Towns,"Who was towns county named after
",<MISC>Your Show Time</MISC> is an <MISC>American</MISC> anthology drama series that debuted on <ORG>NBC Television</ORG> on the <LOC><LOC>East</LOC> Coast</LOC> in September 1948 and then on both the <LOC>East</LOC> and <LOC>West Coasts</LOC>,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
449,Live at Tin Angel,/music/album/artist,Susan Werner,"Who is the album live at tin angel by
",<MISC>Live at Tin Angel</MISC> is the second self-published album by <MISC>American</MISC> singer-songwriter <PER>Susan Werner</PER>,<PER>Susan <PER>Werner</PER></PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> singer-songwriter. Much of <PER>Werner</PER>'s work has been in the contemporary folk genre.
450,Joseph George Rosengarten,/people/person/place_of_birth,Pennsylvania,"where was the birthplace of joseph george rosengarten
",<PER>Joseph George Rosengarten</PER> was a <LOC>Philadelphia</LOC> lawyer,<ORG>Pennsylvania</ORG>
451,John Moores,/people/person/gender,Male,"What is john moores's gender?
453,Diamond,/location/location/people_born_here,Paul Miller,"Who was born in diamond?
",<LOC>Diamond</LOC> is a city in north central <LOC>Newton County</LOC>,<PER>Paul <PER>Miller</PER></PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> newspaper executive and journalist. He headed the <ORG>Gannett</ORG> newspaper chain from 1957 to 1973. <PER>Miller</PER> also served as the top official of the <ORG>Associated Press</ORG> from 1963 to 1977.
457,Masada: Tet,/music/album/genre,Jazz,"Where kind of album is tet
460,Alternative metal,/music/genre/artists,Steelheart,"what artist makes alternative metal?
",<PER>David Kirby</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> poet and the <PER>Robert O. Lawton</PER> Distinguished Professor of <MISC>English</MISC> at <ORG>Florida State University</ORG>.,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
467,It Was the Best of Times,/music/album/artist,Supertramp,"who is the singer of it was the best of times
",<PER>Malik Asselah</PER> is an <MISC><LOC>Algeria</LOC>n</MISC> footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for the <LOC>Algeria</LOC> national football team.,The goalkeeper
473,Peter Menzies Jr.,/film/cinematographer/film,Kangaroo Jack,"what film did peter menzies jr. do cinematography for
",<PER>Peter Gary Menzies Jr</PER>.,<MISC>Kangaroo Jack</MISC> is a 2003 buddy comedy film produced by <ORG>Castle Rock Entertainment</ORG> and <ORG>Jerry Bruckheimer Films</ORG>
",<PER>Aris T. Allen</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> politician who was the first African-<MISC>American</MISC> chair of the <LOC>Maryland</LOC> <MISC>Republican</MISC> party and the first to run for a statewide office in <LOC>Maryland</LOC>.,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
477,Carlo Boszhard,/people/person/gender,Male,"What is carlo boszhard's gender
480,Wyclef Jean,/music/artist/genre,Dancehall,"what island music does wyclef jean create
483,Writer,/people/profession/people_with_this_profession,Alastair Reynolds,"what British science fiction author and writer specializes in dark hard science fiction and space opera?
490,Terry Carr,/book/author/works_written,Universe 1,"what is one of terry carrs written works
",<PER>Terry Gene Carr</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> science fiction fan,<MISC>Universe 1</MISC> is an anthology of original science fiction short stories edited by <PER>Terry Carr</PER>
491,Los Angeles,/location/location/people_born_here,Jordan Cronenweth,"Which famous cinematographer was born in los angeles?
",<ORG>Los Angeles</ORG>,<PER>Jordan Scott Cronenweth</PER>
493,Democratic Party,/government/political_party/ideology,Liberalism,"what ideology does the democratic party follow?
494,Suspense,/film/film_genre/films_in_this_genre,Sneakers,"what is a suspense film
",Suspense is a state of mental uncertainty,<MISC>Sneakers</MISC> is a 1992 <MISC>American</MISC> thriller film directed by <PER>Phil Alden Robinson</PER>
",<PER>Georgius Agricola</PER> was a <MISC>German</MISC> Humanist scholar,<ORG>Germany</ORG>
502,Jamie Masson,/people/person/nationality,Scotland,"What is the nationality of jamie masson?
504,Tonet,/people/person/place_of_birth,Barcelona,"in what country was tonet born
512,Anthony Green,/music/artist/genre,Experimental rock,"what genre does the artist anthony green (musician) perform in
",<PER>Anthony Green</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> singer and musician from <LOC>Doylestown</LOC>,Experimental rock
513,Ahmed Marcouch,/people/person/profession,Politician,"What is Ahmed Marcouch's profession?
517,Windsor,/location/location/people_born_here,John Fitch,"Name someone who was born in windsor.
",<LOC>Windsor</LOC> is a town in <LOC>Hartford County</LOC>,<PER>John Fitch</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> inventor
523,The Jerky Boys: The Movie,/film/film/production_companies,Touchstone Pictures,"WHich production company did the jerky boys: the movie
",The Jerky Boys: The Movie,<ORG>Touchstone Pictures</ORG> was an <MISC>American</MISC> film distribution label of <ORG>Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures</ORG>
526,SPV GmbH,/music/record_label/artist,Heaven &amp; Hell,"Who is an artist from the spv gmbh record label
",<ORG>SPV GmbH</ORG> is a <MISC>German</MISC> independent record label. Founded on 1 January 1984,Heaven &amp; Hell was a <MISC>British-American</MISC> heavy metal supergroup active from 2006 to 2010. The band was a collaboration between <ORG>Black Sabbath</ORG> founding members <PER>Tony Iommi</PER> and <PER>Geezer Butler</PER> and former <ORG>Black Sabbath</ORG> and <ORG>Dio</ORG> members Ronnie James <ORG>Dio</ORG> and <PER>Vinny Appice</PER>. 
529,Heligoland,/location/location/people_born_here,Eva von der Osten,"who is  a person that was born in  heligoland
",<LOC>Heligoland</LOC> is a small archipelago in the <LOC>North Sea</LOC>. A part of the <MISC>German</MISC> state of <LOC>Schleswig-Holstein</LOC> since 1890,<PER>Eva Helga Bertha von der Osten</PER> was a <MISC>German</MISC> soprano.
530,Osaka,/location/location/people_born_here,Akira Nishimura,"what musician was born in osaka
535,Victor Basa,/people/person/place_of_birth,Quezon City,"Where was victor basa born
",<PER>Victor Emmanuel Basa</PER> is a <MISC>Filipino</MISC> model,<ORG>Quezon City</ORG>
538,Kevin McCarthy,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,Hyannis,"Where was kevin mccarthy (actor)'s place of death?
",<PER>Kevin McCarthy</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> stage,<LOC>Hyannis</LOC> is the largest of the seven villages in the town of <LOC>Barnstable</LOC>
"
555,Withlacoochee River,/geography/river/mouth,Gulf of Mexico,"What is at the mouth of the withlacoochee river?
556,Newton College,/location/location/containedby,Lima,"Where is newton college
561,Kurt Bolender,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,Hagen,"Where did kurt bolender pass away
",<PER>Heinz Kurt Bolender</PER> was an <ORG>SS</ORG> sergeant during the <MISC>Nazi</MISC> era. In 1942,<LOC>Hagen</LOC> is the 41st-largest city in <LOC>Germany</LOC>. The municipality is located in the state of <LOC>North Rhine-Westphalia</LOC>. It is located on the south eastern edge of the <LOC>Ruhr</LOC> area
563,They Came from the Sun,/music/album/genre,Post-rock,"what genre is they came from the sun?
567,Alternative rock,/music/genre/albums,Hello Angel,"what is an alternative rock album?
571,Cayucos,/location/hud_county_place/county,San Luis Obispo County,"which county does cayucos belong to
",<LOC>Cayucos</LOC> is an unincorporated coastal town in <LOC>San Luis Obispo County</LOC>,<LOC>San Luis Obispo County</LOC>
",<PER>Darwan Singh Negi VC</PER> was one of the first <MISC>Indian</MISC> soldiers to be awarded the <MISC>Victoria Cross</MISC>,<MISC>World War I</MISC> or the <MISC>First World War</MISC>
574,Haiti,/meteorology/cyclone_affected_area/cyclones,Tropical Storm Claudette,"what is a cyclone that affected haiti
576,Valerie Solanas,/people/deceased_person/place_of_death,San Francisco,"where did valerie solanas pass away
",<PER>Valerie Jean Solanas</PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> radical feminist known for the <MISC>SCUM Manifesto</MISC>,<LOC>San Francisco</LOC>
",<ORG>Vulfpeck</ORG> is an <MISC>American</MISC> funk group founded in 2011. The band has released four EPs,Rhythm and blues
581,Then and Now,/film/film/country,Philippines,"WHich nation filmed then and now
",Noon at Ngayon: Pagsasamang Kay Ganda is a 2003 <MISC>Filipino</MISC> drama film directed by <PER>Marilou Diaz-Abaya</PER> and written by <PER>Ricky Lee</PER>. <MISC>Noon At Ngayon</MISC> tells the story of four friends,<ORG>The Philippines</ORG>
583,Final Fantasy II,/cvg/computer_videogame/platforms,Nintendo Entertainment System,"Which video game platform is final fantasy ii played on?
585,Hrishikesh Mukherjee,/film/director/film,Jurmana,"what's the title of a hrishikesh mukherjee film
",<PER>Hrishikesh Mukherjee</PER> was an <MISC>Indian</MISC> film director,<MISC>Jurmana</MISC> is a 1979 <MISC>Hindi</MISC> romantic drama film. It was produced by <PER>Debesh Gosh</PER> and directed by <PER>Hrishikesh Mukherjee</PER>. The film stars <PER>Amitabh Bachchan</PER>
592,Arabella,/music/composition/language,German language,"what language is arabella in?
599,Space opera,/book/book_subject/works,Komarr,"What is a book that has to do with space opera
601,Country music,/music/genre/albums,Unearthed,"What's a country album by johnny cash
606,Casey Hudson,/cvg/cvg_designer/games_designed,Mass Effect,"cvg designer casey hudson designed what game
",<PER>Casey Hudson</PER> is a <MISC>Canadian</MISC> video game developer,<MISC>Mass Effect</MISC> is an action role-playing game developed by <ORG>BioWare</ORG> and originally released for the <MISC>Xbox 360</MISC> in 2007. It is the first game in the <MISC>Mass Effect</MISC> series
608,Indiana,/location/location/contains,The Children's Museum of Indianapolis,"What's a museum within indiana
610,Portland,/film/film_location/featured_in_films,Paranoid Park,"what locations in portland are featured in films?
612,"Alfonso, Duke of Anjou and Cádiz",/people/person/religion,Catholic Church,"which religion is alfonso, duke of anjou and cádiz
",<PER>Alfonso</PER>,The <ORG>Catholic Church</ORG>
614,Haruki Kadokawa,/film/producer/film,Fall Guy,"what is a movie produced by haruki kadokawa
",<PER>Haruki Kadokawa</PER> is a <MISC>Japanese</MISC> publisher,<MISC>Fall Guy</MISC> is a 1982 <MISC>Japanese</MISC> film directed by <PER>Kinji Fukasaku</PER>
615,Tip Top,/location/location/containedby,Yavapai County,"where is tip top located
617,Adam and Company,/organization/organization/legal_structure,Limited company,"what is the legal structure of the organization adam and company
",<ORG>Adam and Company</ORG> is a trading division of <ORG>The Royal Bank of Scotland</ORG> plc catering for the needs of private bank customers based in the <LOC>United Kingdom</LOC>. ,In a limited company
619,Anil Sharma,/film/producer/film,Aashiq,"what film did anil sharma produce 
",<PER>Anil Sharma</PER> is an <MISC>Indian</MISC> film director and producer.,"<MISC>Aashiq</MISC> is a 2001 <MISC>Indian Hindi</MISC> action romance film directed by <PER>Indra Kumar</PER>. The film stars <PER>Bobby Deol</PER> and <PER>Karisma Kapoor</PER> in the lead. It is a remake of <MISC>Telugu</MISC> movie <MISC>Gulabi</MISC>.
The film premiered on 26 January 2001 in <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>. <MISC>Aashiq</MISC> was declared ""Average"" by <ORG>Box Office India</ORG>."
622,Danger in the Past,/music/album/release_type,Album,"How was danger in the past released
624,Fantasy,/media_common/literary_genre/stories_in_this_genre,The Dead Man,"what is a story in the fantasy genre
",Fantasy is a genre of speculative fiction involving magical elements,"""<MISC>The Dead Man</MISC>"" is a short story by <MISC>Argentinian</MISC> writer <PER>Jorge Luis Borges</PER>. It was first published in the magazine <ORG>Sur</ORG> in November 1946 and appears in the 1949 short story collection <MISC>The Aleph</MISC>."
625,Buster Rhymes,/people/person/place_of_birth,Miami,"What city was buster rhymes born in?
","George ""Buster"" Rhymes is a former professional <MISC>American</MISC> football wide receiver.",<ORG>Miami</ORG>
627,Joe Cusack,/people/person/gender,Male,"what's joe cusack's gender
","<PER>Joseph E. <PER>Cusack</PER></PER> was an <MISC>American</MISC> football player and an officer in the <ORG>United States Army</ORG>.
",<LOC>Butler Township</LOC> is one of fourteen townships in <LOC>Miami County</LOC>,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
632,Mars Global Surveyor,/spaceflight/spacecraft/manufacturer,Jet Propulsion Laboratory,"who created the mars global surveyor 
634,Americas,/location/location/people_born_here,Raynal Bolling,"who is a person that was born in the americas
",<ORG>The Americas</ORG>,<PER>Raynal Cawthorne Bolling</PER> was the first high-ranking officer of the <ORG>United States Army</ORG> to be killed in combat in <MISC>World War I</MISC>. A corporate lawyer by vocation
",<MISC>Deadly Blessing</MISC> is a 1981 <MISC>American</MISC> slasher film directed by <PER>Wes Craven</PER>. The film tells the story of a strange figure committing murder in a contemporary community that is not far from another community that believes in ancient evil and curses. ,The <LOC>United States of America</LOC>
637,Cradle Will Rock,/film/film/cinematography,Jean-Yves Escoffier,"who did the cinematography for the film cradle will rock
",<MISC>Cradle Will Rock</MISC> is a 1999 <MISC>American</MISC> historical drama film written,<PER>Jean-Yves Escoffier</PER> was a <MISC>French</MISC> cinematographer.
645,Sandro Puppo,/people/person/gender,Male,"is sandro puppo male or female
646,American football,/sports/sport/teams,SMU Mustangs football,"Name an american football sports team
",<MISC>American</MISC> football,The <ORG>SMU Mustangs</ORG> football program is a college football team representing <ORG>Southern Methodist University</ORG> in <LOC>University Park</LOC> in <LOC>Dallas County</LOC>
647,Stephen King,/film/writer/film,The Stand,"What television series is an adaptation of a novel by stephen king?
651,Guinea-Bissau,/location/location/time_zones,UTC±00:00,"which time zone is guinea-bissau in?
",<PER>Cem Can</PER> is a <MISC>Turkish</MISC> football player who plays as a midfielder.,In the sport of association football
",The <LOC>Will Marion Cook House</LOC> is a historic townhouse at 221 <LOC>West 138th Street</LOC>,<LOC>New York</LOC>
658,Christine Sinclair,/people/person/place_of_birth,Burnaby,"Where in canada was christine sinclair born
",<PER>Christine Margaret Sinclair OC OLY</PER> is a <MISC>Canadian</MISC> professional soccer player who plays as a forward and captains both National Women's Soccer League club <ORG>Portland Thorns FC</ORG> and the <MISC>Canadian</MISC> national team. ,<LOC>Burnaby</LOC> is a city in the <LOC>Lower Mainland</LOC> region of <LOC>British Columbia</LOC>
665,Montclair,/location/location/people_born_here,Dean Hamer,"who was born in montclair
",<LOC>Montclair</LOC> is a township in <LOC>Essex County</LOC>,<PER>Dean Hamer</PER> is an <MISC>American</MISC> scientist
668,KVAL-TV,/broadcast/broadcast/area_served,Eugene,"What city does kval-tv broadcast to
",<ORG>KVAL-TV</ORG> is a television station in <LOC>Eugene</LOC>,<LOC>Eugene</LOC> is a city in the <LOC>U.S.</LOC> state of <LOC>Oregon</LOC>
670,Dagoba,/music/artist/genre,Thrash metal,"What type of metal does dagoba perform
674,Blues,/music/genre/albums,Don't Look Back,"What is the name of a blues album
675,Bare,/music/album/genre,Adult contemporary music,"What type of music is the album bare (annie lennox album)?
678,Racing game,/cvg/cvg_genre/games,Excitebike 64,"What is an example of a racing game
","<MISC>Minimo</MISC> was a project to create a version of the <ORG>Mozilla</ORG> web browser for small devices like personal digital assistants and mobile phones.
681,Bernard Fanning,/music/artist/label,Dew Process,"who is bernard fanning signed with
","<PER>Bernard Fanning</PER> is an <MISC>Australian</MISC> musician and singer-songwriter. He is the lead vocalist of <LOC>Queensland</LOC> alternative rock band <ORG>Powderfinger</ORG> from its formation in 1989.
",<ORG>Dew Process</ORG> is an <MISC>Australian</MISC> independent record label
683,Maxim Gorky,/influence/influence_node/influenced,Joan Salvat-Papasseit,"whom did  maxim gorky influence
",<PER>Alexei Maximovich Peshkov</PER>,<PER>Joan Salvat-Papasseit</PER> was a <MISC>Catalan</MISC> poet
684,Love Affair,/music/artist/label,CBS Records,"what label is the artist love affair apart of
686,Theodor Billroth Operating,/visual_art/artwork/art_form,Painting,"what type of art form is theodor billroth operating?
",The <PER>Theodor Billroth</PER> Operating painting by <PER>Adalbert Seligmann</PER> shows the <MISC>German</MISC> surgeon <PER>Theodor Billroth</PER> operating in the auditorium of <LOC>Vienna General Hospital</LOC>,Painting is the practice of applying paint
687,35 mm movie film,/film/film_format/film_format,Maria Full of Grace,"What film was recorded using 35 mm film
",35 mm film is a film gauge used in filmmaking,<MISC>Maria Full of Grace</MISC> is a 2004 drama film written and directed by <PER>Joshua Marston</PER>. The film was produced between <LOC>Colombia</LOC> and the <LOC>United States</LOC>. The story follows a <LOC>Colombia</LOC>n girl who becomes a drug mule for a trafficking ring. 
688,Get Ready,/music/album/genre,Electronica,"what type of music is on get ready?
694,Jan Svěrák,/people/person/ethnicity,Czechs,"What is jan svěrák's ethnicity?
",<PER>Jan Svěrák</PER> is a <MISC>Czech</MISC> film director. He is the son of screenwriter and actor <PER>Zdeněk Svěrák</PER>. He studied documentary filmmaking at the <ORG>FAMU</ORG>. ,The <MISC>Czechs</MISC>
696,Michael Baigent,/book/author/works_written,The Jesus Papers,"what did michael baigent write
",<PER>Michael Baigent</PER> was a writer,The Jesus Papers: Exposing the Greatest Cover-Up in History is a book by author <PER>Michael Baigent</PER> published in 2006. Providing his detailed history of <PER>Jesus'</PER> life and crucifixion
698,Shadows in Flight,/book/book/genre,Science fiction,"whats the genre for the book titled shadows in flight
701,Gremlin Interactive,/cvg/cvg_developer/games_developed,Toyota Celica GT Rally,"What is a game developed by gremlin interactive?
